Guide to the Time Inc. Corporate Public Affairs Department Records 1945-2000 (bulk 1959-1996) MS 3009-RG 19
New-York Historical Society
- Series III. Radio/TV Publicity Office Files, 1974-1990; 2.5 Linear feet in 3 record cartons
  - Time: Washington Bureau Chief Party, 1989 (Offsite-box 1748, Folder 21)
  - Time: WMCA Radio, 1983 (Offsite-box 1748, Folder 22-23)
  - Time World Newsradio, 1984 (Offsite-box 1748, Folder 24)
- Series IV. Corporate Community Relations Office Files, 1990-2000; 3 Linear feet in 3 record cartons
  Corporate Community Relations Office Files include records on various public interest programs and projects conducted by Time Inc. including yearly overview reports and records on exhibitions.
  It's US: A Celebration of Who We Are in America Today was a traveling photographic exhibition with a related student essay contest, lectures and publications created by Time Inc. as part of a diversity project.
  According to the finding aid in the Archives of the Museum of Fine Arts, Houston, Songs of My People was a book project developed by D. Michael Cheers, Eric Easter, and Dudley M. Brooks, and had Time Warner Cable as a major sponsor. The project included a traveling exhibition, a music video, and a lecture series. Smithsonian Institution Traveling Exhibition Services was the domestic exhibition sponsor, and United States Information Agency was the international exhibition sponsor. The records in this series are primarily papers on the traveling exhibition, copies of related publications, and audiovisual of the music video. Unreformatted audiovisual material in the collection is not accessible.
  Organized alphabetically.
  - Community / Social Responsibility Reports, 1990-2000 (Offsite-box 3291, Folder 1-2)
  - It's US: A Celebration of Who We Are in America Today, 1993-1997 (Offsite-box 2302)
    Records include educational material; correspondence with Don Wise Designs and Stonesong Press; memoranda on photograph research, planning, concept clarification, project overview and costs; action plans; and promotional material. The folders called "Originals" contain materials distributed to participants including progress updates, press releases, the essay contest overview, and excerpts from contest winners. The records are primarily from Vice President of Corporate Community Relations Toni Fay.
    Audiovisual includes:
    1 videocassette (VHS) (67 min.): 1/2 in. On container: "Fratelli Group. Russell Senate Tapes 4, 5, 6. Haddow Communications. It's US. Panel Discussion. Arthur Schlesinger and Others. 11/29/95. TRT: 67:00."
    1 videocassette (VHS): 1/2 in. On label: "NY1 News Special. "It's US"."
  - Songs of My People: Papers, 1990-1998 (Offsite-box 3291, Folder 3-29)
    Papers include records from the 1991 planning conference of the traveling exhibit, correspondence with the exhibition sponsors, lists of participating museums, brochures, exhibition guides, pins, press kits, and materials from the exhibitions venues in Australia, South Africa, and Washington, D.C. The folder on South Africa includes a brochure and photographs from a Michael Cheers workshop.
  - Songs of My People: Audiovisual and Publications, 1992-1994 (Offsite-box 2510)
    Records includes audiovisual material:
    1 videocassette (U-matic). On label: "'Exposing Hidden Windows,' Producer, Michael Cheers, New African Visions, Inc. (RT: 29:46) and the 'Songs of My People Music Video,' Executive Producers, Glenda Bryant and Monica Sutton (RT: 14:40) Total Runing Time: 45:00."
    1 video reel (C Format). On label: "New African Productions, Inc. Producer: Michael Cheers. 'Exposing Hidden Windows.' African American Photographers. TRT: 29:46. Dub Master. 1/8/92. Same Audio Both Ch's."
    1 video reel (C Format). On label: "Songs of My People. 14:39." On container: "Actual Music Video Master."
    2 videocassettes (VHS) (14 min., 39 sec). On label: "Songs of My People. African Americans: A Self-Portrait. Music Video Single."
- Series V. Chief Speechwriter Peter Quinn Files, 1972-2000; 9 Linear feet in 9 record cartons
  Corporate Public Affairs vice president Donald Wilson's files indicate that Peter Quinn took over for Bob Rackleff as Chief Speechwriter in 1981 and lists the position as part of Corporate Public Affairs. Wilson's files do not record when Rackleff became Chief Speechwriter or when Time Inc. created the position.
  Records includes background materials and research, presumably to write speeches, and final copies of speeches for executives throughout Time Inc. Speeches in the speech files may have been written by Peter Quinn or his predecessor Bob Rackleff.
  - Analysts Meeting, 1988 (Offsite-box 1763, Folder 1)
  - Annual Meeting of Shareholders, 1987 (Offsite-box 1763, Folder 2)
  - Annual Reports, 1972-1979 (Offsite-box 1763, Folder 3)
  - Articles and Statements: Davidson, Ralph P., 1985 (Offsite-box 1763, Folder 4)
  - Articles and Miscellaneous: Sutton, Kelso, undated (Offsite-box 1763, Folder 5)
  - Discs [RESTRICTED], 1986-1998 (Offsite-box 2124)
    Includes discs with a variety of names, departments, offices, subsidiaries and topics written on them.
    108 computer discs (floppy disk): 5 1/4 in.
    13 computer discs (floppy disk): 3 1/2 in.
  - Financial Analysts Meeting, 1987 (Offsite-box 1763, Folder 6)
  - Financial Statements, 1984 (Offsite-box 1763, Folder 7)
  - Grunwald, Henry, 1981-1987 (Offsite-box 1763, Folder 8-9)
  - Levin, Gerald: "Values for the Digital Age: The Legacy of Henry Luce", 2000 (Offsite-box 1763, Folder 10)
  - Lyford Cay Transcript (of Strategic Planning), 1985 (Offsite-box 2173, Folder 1)
  - Merger: Time Warner, 1989 (Offsite-box 2173, Folder 2-5)
  - Munro, J. Richard, 1985-1988 (Offsite-box 2173, Folder 6)
  - New York Historical Records Advisory Board, 1986-1987 (Offsite-box 2173, Folder 7-9)
  - News Releases: Quarterly Reports, 1985-1988 (Offsite-box 2173, Folder 10)
  - Newsletters: Vital Speeches of the Day, 1987 (Offsite-box 2843, Folder 1)
  - Newsletters: Winners & Sinners, 1987-1989 (Offsite-box 2843, Folder 2)
  - Nicholas, N. J. (Nick), 1986-1992 (Offsite-box 2173, Folder 11-12)
  - Paramount's Bid for Time Inc., 1989 (Offsite-box 2173, Folder 13)
  - Scripts, 1986-1987 (Offsite-box 2173, Folder 14)
  - Speeches: General: 1985 October-1986 February, 1985-1986 (Offsite-box 2173, Folder 15-19)
  - Speeches: General: 1986 March-1989 December, 1986-1989 (Offsite-box 1764)
  - Speeches: General: 1990 January-1996, 1990-1996 (Offsite-box 1923, Folder 1-8)
  - Speeches: General: 1990 September-1991 July, 1990-1991 (Offsite-box 2843, Folder 3-13)
  - Speeches: General: 1991 September-1992 June, 1991-1992 (Offsite-box 2843, Folder 14-23)
  - Speeches: General: 1992 September-1993 June, 1992-1993 (Offsite-box 2843, Folder 24-33)
  - Speeches: Brack, Reginald K., 1987-1994 (Offsite-box 1923, Folder 9)
  - Speeches: Britt, Glenn, 1988 (Offsite-box 1923, Folder 10)
  - Speeches: Cathcart, Mel, 1992 (Offsite-box 1923, Folder 11)
  - Speeches: Davidson, Ralph P., 1985-1987 (Offsite-box 1923, Folder 12-14)
  - Speeches: Dingman, Michael, 1989-1990 (Offsite-box 1923, Folder 15)
  - Speeches: Fuchs, Michael, 1988-1995 (Offsite-box 1923, Folder 16)
  - Speeches: Hayes, Jim, 1987 (Offsite-box 1923, Folder 17)
  - Speeches: Meigher, Christopher, 1986-1991 (Offsite-box 1923, Folder 18)
  - Speeches: Miller, Robert L., 1985 (Offsite-box 1923, Folder 19)
  - Speeches: Morgado, Robert J., 1991-1992 (Offsite-box 1923, Folder 20)
  - Speeches: Munro, J. Richard: 1985 October-1986 April, 1985-1986 (Offsite-box 1923, Folder 21-23)
  - Speeches: Munro, J. Richard: 1986 March-1989 June, 1988-1993 (Offsite-box 1924)
  - Speeches: Munro, J. Richard: 1989 September-1999, 1989-1999 (Offsite-box 1925)
  - Speeches: Outside Time Inc., 1984-1991 (Offsite-box 1926, Folder 1)
  - Speeches: Payson, Martin, 1992 (Offsite-box 1926, Folder 2)
  - Speeches: Rackleff, Bob, 1980-1985 (Offsite-box 1926, Folder 3-6)
  - Speeches: Ross, Courtney Sale, 1991-1992 (Offsite-box 1926, Folder 7)
  - Speeches: Ross, Steven J., 1990-1991 (Offsite-box 1926, Folder 8-9)
  - Speeches: Sutton, Kelso, 1985-1987 (Offsite-box 1926, Folder 10)
  - Speeches: Thomas, Richard B., 1987 (Offsite-box 1926, Folder 11)
  - Speeches: Wilson, Donald M., 1986-1996 (Offsite-box 1926, Folder 12)
  - Strategy Dinner, 1986 (Offsite-box 1926, Folder 13)
  - Time Inc.: Corporate Identity, Mission, and Strategy, 1984-1988 (Offsite-box 1926, Folder 14-18)
  - Time-Life Books, 1983-1986 (Offsite-box 1926, Folder 19)
  - United Negro College Fund, 1986-1990 (Offsite-box 2843, Folder 34)
  - Volunteerism, 1987 (Offsite-box 2843, Folder 35)
  - Whittle Communications, 1992 (Offsite-box 2843, Folder 36)
  - Women, 1983-1988 (Offsite-box 2843, Folder 37)
- Series VI. Special Events Manager Ann Bellows Files, 1963-1996 (bulk, 1995-1996); 1.5 Linear feet in 3 record cartons
  These files were accompanied by a transfer form from Ann Bellows sending records on the 1996 Atlanta Summer Olympics, a 1995 newstour, and historical newstour materials to the Time Inc. Archives.
  The newstour files are similar to the newstour administrative files in the Time Publishing and Business Records, and the Olympics files are similar to those in Jelmir Lucas's files. Corporate Public Affairs may have taken over the arrangement of these events from Time Promotion and Public Affairs in later years.
  Older newstour materials that encompassed entire folders or binders were returned to the Time Promotion and Public Affairs files. Files containing assembled historical records remain here with Bellows's files. Newstour records include a briefing binder on the various locations; itineraries and agenda; lists of and biographies on participants; invoices and bills; and branded stationary and other printed material.
  Olympics contains her work coordinating Olympics tickets, travel, and accommodations for Time Inc. staff and corporate guests for the 1996 summer games in Atlanta when Time Inc. was a sponsor. The materials include lists of participants, the scheduled program, and branded material including a selection of pins.
  - Archives Transfer Form, 1996 (Offsite-box 2326, Folder 3)
  - Newstours: Newstour 1995 (Offsite-box 2326, Folder 4-19)
    This newstour traveled to Cuba, Lebanon, India, Vietnam, Russia, and Hong Kong.
  - Newstours: Newstour 1995 [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R39)
  - Newstours: Historical Material, 1963-1995 (Offsite-box 2326, Folder 20-24)
    While planning the 1995 newstour, Bellows collected material from earlier newstours such as prior descriptions and participant lists.
  - Olympics: Summer Olympics 1996 (Offsite-box 3290, Folder 8-14)
  - Olympics: Summer Olympics 1996 [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R39)
- Series VII. Exhibition Files from the Reception Center, Exhibit Hall, and Exhibition Center, 1949-1972; 15.5 Linear feet in 8 record cartons and 5 flat boxes
  Time Inc. displayed exhibitions in public areas of their offices at the Time & Life Building at 9 Rockefeller Plaza and in the new Time & Life Building at 1271 Avenue of the Americas in the Rockefeller Center. The public areas are referred to as the Reception Center, Exhibit Hall, and Exhibition Center. It isn't clear if these are three separate areas or if they are areas with several names. were renamed.
  Some exhibitions showcase Time Inc.'s history or photographs produced by Time Inc. magazines. Exhibitions may be organized by one of the Time Inc. magazines, may be co-organized by Time Inc. and an outside group, or may be a loan of a traveling exhibition from another institution. Several early exhibitions came from the American Federation of Arts.
  Based on the creators of the records, exhibitions in the Reception Center, exhibit Hall, or Exhibition Center in the Time & Life Building were managed separately from the traveling exhibitions used for promotion, although there is some exhibits were reprised for travel.
  Several people and offices oversaw the organization and implementation of the exhibitions including Bernard Barnes, head of Corporate Special Projects, along with his assistants over time Richard Amill, John Wingerter, John C. Byers, Elizabeth Hanson, and Wells Walker; Edgar P. Smith, assistant to the Time Inc. president; and Bernard Yudain, the assistant to the Time Inc. president in regards to public affairs. By 1968 Barnes is no longer with Time Inc., and Hanson is now in the Central Services Division (later renamed Company Services) as Exhibition Hall manager. By 1972, she is no longer with Company Services, but the Exhibition Hall is still managed as part of this division.
  These files are located within the Corporate Public Affairs record group because the earliest version of Corporate Publicity was overseen by the head of Corporate Special Projects according to the Time Inc. Department Head Lists, and an archives transfer form indicates some of the material from Exhibition Center exhibits was the property of Corporate Public Affairs.
  In 1970 Time Inc. creates the department Corporate Public Affairs. By 1978 Corporate Public Affairs includes Corporate Creative Services which, among other tasks, oversaw exhibits in the Time Inc. buildings or traveling exhibits sponsored by Time Inc. Around 1986, Corporate Cultural Affairs is created, which may have replaced Creative Services, fully focusing on exhibits.
  Records document exhibitions shown in the public spaces of the the Time & Life Building at 9 Rockefeller Plaza and in the new Time & Life Building at 1271 Avenue of the Americas in the Rockefeller Center. The majority of files document exhibitions at the second building with one folder listing exhibitions from the first building. Included are some files discussing sculpture in the plaza.
  Records come from Bernard Barnes, head of Corporate Special Projects, and his assistants Richard Amill, John Wingerter, John C. Byers, Elizabeth Hanson, and Wells Walker; and Edgar P. Smith, assistant to the Time Inc. president. The majorty of later files come from Hanson in her role as Exhibition Hall Manager with some from Bernard Yudain, the assistant to the Time Inc. president in regards to public affairs.
  There is some overlap of exhibitions represented in the records kept by Time Life International/Corporate International on the international traveling exhibitions in this record group and by the Promotion and Public Affairs Department in the Time Publishing and Business Records.
  This series is organized into three subseries:
  Subseries VII.A. Administrative Files
  Subseries VII.B. Exhibition Files
  Subseries VII.C. Recurring Exhibition Files
  - Subseries VII.A. Administrative Files, 1961-1972; 0.34 Linear feet in 6 folders
    The Administrative Files contain records regarding running the Reception Center and Exhibition Center and are not focused on any one exhibition. The records include correspondence, drawings, and invoices regarding fabrication of triagular steel sign to announce exhibitions, receipts for equipment purchased or loaned, and attendance statistics compared against major New York City museums. Of interest are records on commissioning artwork to place on the granite plinth over the entrance to the subway and include images of design proposals from Charles Eames and photographs of a test installation. Ultimately "Cubed Curve" by William Crovello was installed in this location, but there are no records in this series about it.
    Organized alphabetically with arrangement determined by the archivist.
    - Archives Transfer Form, 1975 (Offsite-box 4046, Folder 1a)
    - Insurance, 1961-1972 (Offsite-box 4046, Folder 1b)
    - Plaza Sign, 1961-1967 (Offsite-box 4046, Folder 2)
    - Plinth (Plaza), 1966 (Offsite-box 4046, Folder 3)
    - Projectors and Equipment, 1961-1968 (Offsite-box 4046, Folder 4)
    - Reception Center Attendance Figures vs. Museums, 1961-1962 (Offsite-box 4046, Folder 5)
  - Subseries VII.B. Exhibition Files, 1959-1970; 9 Linear feet in 5 record cartons and 3 flat boxes
    Records include correspondence from co-organizers; correspondence and memoranda regarding installation, shipping, proposals, loans, and insurance; exhibition catalogs and brochures; press releases; press clippings; photographic material depicting installed exhibitions; floor plans; and wall text and labels.
    Organized chronologically by the exhibition opening based on the original arrangement.
    - 1950-1960: Old Time & Life Building, 1959-1960 (Offsite-box 4046, Folder 6)
    - 1961 January 23: Since Time Began, 1960-1962 (Offsite-box 4046, Folder 7)
    - 1961 April 14: Latin America: New Departures, 1960-1961 (Offsite-box 4046, Folder 8)
    - 1961 May 17: Eisenstaedt: Witness to His Times (Offsite-box 4046, Folder 9)
    - 1961 June 5: Famous Likenesses (Offsite-box 4046, Folder 10-11)
    - 1961 July 8: Form Givers [empty] (Offsite-box 4046, Folder 12)
    - 1961 August 5: Cover Quiz (Offsite-box 4046, Folder 13-14)
    - 1961 September 15: West Berlin (Offsite-box 4046, Folder 15-16)
    - 1961 October 28: Upjohn Brain (Offsite-box 4046, Folder 17)
    - 1962 January 24: AT&T / Communicating by Satellite (Offsite-box 4046, Folder 18)
    - 1962 January 24: AT&T / Communicating by Satellite [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R39)
    - 1962 May 5: Italian Sculpture (Offsite-box 4046, Folder 19)
    - 1962 June 8: Berlin Wall (Offsite-box 4046, Folder 20)
    - 1962 June 30: Birth of the Republic, 1960-1970 (Offsite-box 4046, Folder 21-25)
    - 1962 June 30: Birth of the Republic, circa 1962 (Offsite-box 4050, Folder 1)
    - 1962 June 30: Birth of the Republic (Offsite-box 4051, Folder 1-5)
    - 1962 June 30: Birth of the Republic: Rolled Wall Text, Contains one large roll of 17 individual items. (Offsite-box 4052, Item 1-17)
    - 1962 October 5: Early American Folk Arts (Offsite-box 4046, Folder 26-27)
    - 1963 February 15: Retrospect: 1923-1963 (Time's 40th anniversary), 1962-1963 (Offsite-box 4046, Folder 28)
    - 1963 July 16: World's Fair Preview (Offsite-box 4047, Folder 1-2)
    - 1963 September 28: Great Ideas of Western Man (Offsite-box 4047, Folder 3)
    - 1963 November 5: Soviet Graphic Arts (Offsite-box 4047, Folder 4)
    - 1964 January 25: The Photography of Gjon Mili (Offsite-box 4047, Folder 5)
    - 1964 April: World's Fair: Vatican Pavilion, 1962-1965 (Offsite-box 4047, Folder 6)
    - 1964 April 18: Paintings of Famous People (Time Cover Show) (Offsite-box 4047, Folder 7)
    - 1964 May 15: Photographs of France (Offsite-box 4047, Folder 8)
    - 1964 May 20: Time-Life Art for Publication (Offsite-box 4047, Folder 9)
    - 1964 July 8: Mother and Child in Modern Art (Offsite-box 4047, Folder 10)
    - 1964 September 26: Medieval Frescoes from Yugoslavia (Offsite-box 4047, Folder 11)
    - 1964 October 24: Eliot Elisofan, 1965 (Offsite-box 4047, Folder 12)
    - 1965 January 22: Mathematica - A World of Numbers, 1965-1967 (Offsite-box 4047, Folder 13)
    - 1965 May 8: Art of Two Cities, 1964-1965 (Offsite-box 4047, Folder 14)
    - 1965 June 26: Temples of Abu Simbel (Offsite-box 4047, Folder 15)
    - 1965 August 14: Animal Behavior (Offsite-box 4047, Folder 16-20)
    - 1965 October 27: Artzybasheff (Offsite-box 4048, Folder 1)
    - 1966 January 15: The Works of Gordon Parks (Offsite-box 4048, Folder 2)
    - 1966 June 8: 17 Latin American Painters (Offsite-box 4048, Folder 3)
    - 1966 July 9: Industry and the Market Place (Offsite-box 4048, Folder 4)
    - 1966 August 27: Eisenstaedt: Witness to Our Time (Offsite-box 4048, Folder 5)
    - 1966 October 20: Early American Folk Arts, 1965-1966 (Offsite-box 4048, Folder 6-7)
    - 1967 January 21: Heredity and You (Offsite-box 4048, Folder 8)
    - 1967 April 21: A Salute to Canada's Centennial and Expo 67 (Offsite-box 4048, Folder 9-11)
    - 1967 June 27: Pictures of the Year 1966 (Offsite-box 4048, Folder 12)
    - 1967 August 5: America's Great Wilderness (Offsite-box 4048, Folder 13-14)
    - 1967 September 16: Fortune / Art in World Business (Offsite-box 4048, Folder 15-16)
    - 1968 January 20: A Chance to Be Somebody (Offsite-box 4048, Folder 17-19)
    - 1968 May 15: Picasso - The Artist (Offsite-box 4049, Folder 1)
    - 1968 June 28: A Science Tune-In: New Horizons in Light and Sound (Offsite-box 4049, Folder 2-6)
    - 1968 June 28: A Science Tune-In: New Horizons in Light and Sound [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R39)
    - 1968 September 28: The Olympics: ATribute to the Games (Offsite-box 4049, Folder 7-8)
    - 1968 November 18: Made with Paper, 1967 (Offsite-box 4049, Folder 9-10)
    - 1969 July 12: Apollo, 1969-1970 (Offsite-box 4049, Folder 11-14)
    - 1969 July 12: Apollo [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R39)
    - 1969 September 27: Football: The First Hundred Years (Offsite-box 4049, Folder 15-16)
    - 1970 February 5: Agencies' Choice (Offsite-box 4049, Folder 17)
    - Undated: Time and Life Weather Window (Offsite-box 4049, Folder 18)
  - Subseries VII.C. Recurring Exhibitions Files, 1949, 1961-1970; 7.83 Linear feet in 3 record cartons and 2 flat boxes
    Two recurring exhibitions featured in the Time & Life Building Reception or Exhibition Center were the Christmas exhibit and The Sistine Chapel, which was frequently an Easter exhibit. These two exhibitions comprised illuminated large-scale transparency reproductions of master artworks.
    In 1955, the Life staff responsible for the Rockefeller Center lobby Christmas display developed an exhibition showcasing large-size color transparencies. This was based on an exhibit of large transparencies recently produced by Kodak for Grand Central Station in 1950. The Time Inc. exhibit was the first to use the technique to reproduce works of art, showcasing illuminated copies of master works related to the life of Christ. This initial Christmas exhibit inspired the development of the later Illuminations of Fifty Great Paintings exhibit. The Sistine Chapel was part of Illuminations in 1958, then displayed as a separate show.
    Records document the annual Christmas and Easter exhibitions and include correspondence arranging installation and removal; floor plans; examples of wall text; and audiovisual material with the music and narration. Records mainly come from Bernard Yudain and Elizabeth Hanson. Because The Sistine Chapel was a reprisal of part of the initial Illuminations exhibition, there are some records from Corporate Public Affairs staff Jim Alberse and Jeanne Kerr.
    Unreformatted audiovisual material in the collection is not accessible.
    Organized alphabetically with arrangement imposed by the archivist.
    - Christmas Story: General Files, 1961-1969 (Offsite-box 4053, Folder 1-6)
    - Christmas Story: Music, circa 1961 (Offsite-box 4054, Folder 1-2)
      Includes audiovisual material.
      3 audiotape reels (endless tape): analog; 5 1/4 in., 1/4 in. tape.
    - Christmas Story: Narration, 1963-1969 (Offsite-box 4054, Folder 3-6)
      1 audio cartridge (Fidelipac cartridge): analog; 5 1/4 x 4 in., 1/4 in. tape. Label: "Xmas Narration. 12/5/63. 10/16/69."
      1 audio cartridge (Fidelipac cartridge): analog; 5 1/4 x 4 in., 1/4 in. tape. Label: "Xmas Narration. 12/19/63. 10/16/69."
      1 audio cartridge (Fidelipac cartridge): analog; 5 1/4 x 4 in., 1/4 in. tape. Label: "Xmas Narration. 12/12/66."
      2 audio cartridges (Fidelipac cartridge): analog; 5 1/4 x 4 in., 1/4 in. tape. Label: "Christmas Narration. 12/24/69."
    - Christmas Story: Notes for Show in 1970, 1962-1970 (Offsite-box 4053, Folder 7)
    - Christmas Story: Souvenir Brochure, circa 1961-1969 (Offsite-box 4053, Folder 8)
    - Christmas Story: Structural Display Blueprints, 1961 (Offsite-box 4053, Folder 9)
    - Christmas Story: Telephone Tape, circa 1961 (Offsite-box 4054, Folder 7)
      2 audiotape reels (endless tape): analog; 5 1/4 in., 1/4 in. tape.
    - Christmas Story: Wall Text and Labels, circa 1960 (Offsite-box 4050, Folder 2-4)